Jorge Rodríguez Jové

LEVEL DESIGNER



jorgerodriguezdev@gmail.com



Madrid, Spain



+34 636524469

SKILLS

Level Layout and Pacing

Level Blockout

3C's

C# Programming

Game Design Documentation

Environmental Storytelling

Player Psychology / UX Design

Agile

TOOLS

Unreal Engine 5 & Unity
Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator

Google Docs, Slides & Sheets

Basic 3D Modeling in Blender & 3DSMax

Github, SourceTree & P4V

Iira

LINKS

Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/jorgerodriguezjove

Portfolio

jorgerodriguezjove.github.io/

LANGUAGES

- Spanish Native
- English Fluent
- Japanese Beginner

ABOUT ME

I try to play all kinds of video games but, I'm especially interested in games that focus on traversal and movement.

Outside video games, I'm passionate about literature, narrative, and stories with rich worlds and characters.

I'm a **Game and Level Designer** with 4 years of experience between Indie and AAA games. I have experience designing and developing 3D maps as welll as procedural generation systems for 2D levels. I'm a big fan of games focused around movement, exploration and interesting ways of traversal.

WORK EXPERIENCE

LEVEL DESIGNER

NDA Multiplayer FPS

Nimble Giant | Mar 2022 - Aug 2024

I worked for 2.5 years as a Level Designer on an unannounced Multiplayer FPS in a team of almost a hundred people.

- Designing, documenting, and proposing multiple new maps.
- Owner of several map areas, establishing the **vision**, **goals**, and **flow**.
- Implementing, testing, and iterating blockouts in engine.
- Working alongside QA and Environment Artists to achieve a realistic map
 while keeping healthy gameplay.

GAME DESIGNER & C# PROGRAMMER

Ignited Steel

Yocaikade | Jul 2020 - Mar 2022

I worked for almost 2 years developing Ignited Steel, a Turn-Based Tactics published by Meteorbyte Studios and developed by Yokaicade: a small team I created with 5 fellow ex-college classmates.

- Defining the core game design.
- Designing and developing in C# multiple main features: Level and Game Procedural System, Enemy AI, Player Weapons, UI.
- In charge of **Production** and keeping track of **Tasks** and **Deadlines**.
- Balancing and Iterating Enemy and Equipment Statistics.
- Narrative Owner: I wrote all the in-game descriptions and over half of the narrative events.

EDUCATION

B.A DEGREE IN VIDEOGAME DEVELOPMENT

Sep 2016 - Jun 2020

U-Tad

B2 ENGLISH DIPLOMA

2016

Cambridge